I got one disc back.
Just one.
We can bring him back to life.
All I know
is that the disc has this power.
We'll call this operation
the "Savage Garden Plan".
Take him with you.
He'll be able to help you.
His name is Weather Report.
Jumpin' Jack Flash!
Weather Report!
But him, where is he?
I have to get the disc back!
wakatta koto wa amaete naiteru baai janai
S'il y a une chose que je sais, c'est qu'il n'y a pas de temps pour pleurnicher
kibou no ito o tagutte tsukande ugokidasu
J'atteindrai le fil de l'espoir, je l'attraperai et je continuerai mon chemin
harimegurasareru trap and hate kawashiteku
S'étendant tout autour de toi, esquive les pièges et la haine
Okay (Okay) All right (All right)
matta nashi no survival days
Personne ne peut arrêter mes jours de survie
Get away from (Stone Ocean)
Éloigne-toi de (Stone Ocean)
I don't wanna say (There's no chance)
Je ne veux pas dire, (C'est impossible)
Let's get started, count (One, two, three)
C'est parti, compte, (Un, deux, trois)
Take me far away (Fly Stone Free)
Emmène-moi loin, (Vole ! Stone Free)
atashi ga atashi de aru tame ni
Tant que je suis sincère avec moi-même
(Got to be tough)
(Je dois être forte)
Break out (Hey) Mezame yo (Ho)
Explose ! (Hey) Je suis bien debout (Ho)
kinou made no atashi ja irarenai
Je ne veux plus redevenir celle que j'étais avant
Break out (Hey) Donna ni (Ho)
Explose ! (Hey) Peu importe combien (Ho)
michisuu no skill attack saretemo
D'attaques habiles me mettent à mal
genkai wa houkai
Je surpasse mes limites
Give up wa rongai
Hors de question d'abandonner
unmei tenazukeru made
Jusqu'à ce que le destin soit de mon côté...
I don't stop beatin' don't stop beatin'
Je n'arrêterai pas de frapper, n'arrêterai pas de frapper
Don't stop beating 'em up
Je n'arrêterai pas de les frapper
Episode 11   The Savage Garden Plan (To the courtyard!) (2)
Emergency alert activated.
Corridor 7B.
– Yes, corridor 7B.
– Emergency alert activated.
– We're waiting for a report.
– What's causing this commotion?
We have no information.
But corridor 7B only leads
to the workshop.
It can't be a riot.
Rest assured.
Yes, all right.
I have complete trust
in the inmates.
This commotion has made me curious,
that's all.
You surely know
that no one has managed
to escape here in 20 years.
Besides, the courtyard opens onto corridor 7B.
No one would dare escape from there.
Very well.
We'll handle it, Father.
I'll leave you to it, then.
One last question.
Is the clock accurate?
Yes.
It's 11:58.
Almost lunchtime.
Outgoing Calls (Today) Women's Ward
Outgoing Calls (Today)   Women's Ward
At 11:51,
a call to the Speedwagon Foundation.
I have the same request as usual.
I want access to the call log
and the conversation recordings.
Women's prison, booth number 16.
A conversation of about seven minutes.
Weather Report.
Since you touched me,
you don't weigh anything either now.
I don't see our enemy anywhere.
We have to get the disc back.
Calm down.
He must be in this laundry room.
He's hiding somewhere.
The courtyard is behind this door.
This door you're trying to reach
must be locked.
We'll have to use force,
maybe even an explosion.
There's something I have to do.
I know this isn't the time,
but it's something private.
But it's urgent,
and I have to go now.
So, uh...
I don't know why I feel the urge now.
But, uh...
it's something we all have to do.
What is it?
Well,
it's a P-word
related to the pelvic area.
The natural need that brings relief
when it isn't number two.
You need to take a piss.
Don't come up to me just to say that.
I'm serious. I have to go.
Just pick a corner of the room.
Damn it, why am I trying to talk
about this with a guy?
I already relieved myself.
See? It's floating over there.
When the body enters zero gravity,
blood rushes to the head in massive amounts.
The blood usually present
in the lower limbs
colonizes the space between the skin
and the bones of the skull,
causing swelling
known as "moon face."
Furthermore,
the kidneys detect
the danger this poses to the body
from this change in circulation.
They work to reduce
the volume of blood in the body,
which triggers an acute diuretic effect
that reduces blood volume
by expelling salt.
– But...
– No need to be ashamed.
I'll absorb your urine
with my clouds.
What?
Hey, what are these droplets?
Your cloud has a leak!
Weather Report!
No, that's not it.
It's being sucked through
the gap between the doors!
Me too. I'm bleeding.
My wound from earlier.
Blood!
My nose won't stop bleeding!
I'm having trouble breathing...
No, it can't be!
Jolyne!
Everything I touch
enters zero gravity.
I touched the walls around the door.
Which means the entire room
is free of gravity!
The air!
The air is leaving the room, weightless.
The gravitational force
around the room is sucking the air out.
I have to plug this hole.
Otherwise, we'll die of asphyxiation!
Jolyne, you're wrong.
Asphyxiation isn't
our most pressing concern.
Our blood will boil first,
and that's what will kill us.
In a vacuum, blood boils like water.
In a zero-gravity vacuum,
it only takes 20 seconds for blood
to evaporate out of the human body.
Should I reload?
We'll get shot.
We have to hide somewhere!
What are you saying?
My nose is bleeding, I'm draining dry!
Let's stop the air from leaving the room!
Weather Report!
Take short breaths.
I gathered what little air
was left in the room
to cover our bodies in clouds.
Cloud spacesuits.
The room is an almost perfect vacuum.
All the remaining air is here.
Your nosebleed has stopped.
How long will we be able to breathe?
I'd rather not answer that.
I'd say about two minutes.
We're as good as dead in these clouds.
If we don't defeat the enemy
in under two minutes,
we'll vanish into the vacuum,
right?
Precisely.
Where is he?
We have to find him.
Whatever we do,
if he attacks, he'll finish us off.
Now that my nose has stopped bleeding,
I have a question.
Listen, Jolyne.
I said two minutes,
but it might be one.
We have to find him right now!
We're breathing in more and more CO2!
The laundry baskets.
They're not floating.
Those baskets over there.
I touched the walls of this room,
which made the gravity disappear inside
and made the objects float.
So why are these baskets and jerry cans
stuck to the wall
instead of floating?
And then, this enemy.
How is he
breathing in a vacuum?
His blood should be boiling, right?
In other words,
this is the range of his power.
Zero gravity stops
after a certain distance.
This room isn't
entirely affected.
The range of his power, you say?
From here to the laundry baskets,
it's about 20 meters.
Zero gravity stops over there.
If we can get there,
we'll be able to breathe normally.
Go, Weather Report.
He's outside the vacuum zone.
If you don't control the air now,
we'll never catch up with our enemy.
You're probably right.
The other side of this cage.
Go, Weather Report.
I can feel the pressure dropping
inside my spacesuit.
Go before the cloud spacesuit
scatters into the vacuum!
You won't leave
the range of my power!
Are you going to attack him?
I won't let you.
I'll protect Weather Report!
Weather Report
Destructive Power: A
Speed: B
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: A
Destructive Power: A
Speed: B
Range: C
Durability: A
Precision: E
Growth Potential: A
Weather Report
He caught up with me.
I'm charging!
Only a few meters left
before he reaches the oxygen.
Once Weather Report controls the air,
you'll be finished!
If you want air so badly,
go ahead, no problem.
No need to go
all the way to the laundry baskets.
I've already finished
my attack.
I wasn't trying to ricochet
the bullets to hit him.
I was aiming for the jerry can!
There's a little air left inside.
High-pressure air.
Which is going to explode!
Weather Report!
He's entering zero gravity again.
He's done for.
He has nothing to stop his momentum.
Weather Report!
This is the end.
The spacesuit is giving out!
Jolyne! Are you insane?!
Stop!
He's going to shoot you down!
That burst alone
will be enough to scatter your spacesuit!
This woman makes her decisions
at lightning speed.
She's charging at that bastard
to stop his movement
and push him back out
of my power's reach again!
Sadly,
I won't let you!
I knew about it.
Your Stand is very powerful.
My spinning bullets
aren't fast enough against it.
That's why I came prepared.
I searched for them.
I captured them for this very moment.
There are more than I expected.
Rats! They're alive!
Are they...
Stone Free!
Keep this vermin away from me!
I can't see anything!
I didn't expect you
to stand up to me like this.
Checkmate.
You're finished, Jolyne Kujo!
Mission accomplished!
Jumpin' Jack Flash.
Too powerful.
My power is invincible.
What luck to have landed
in this prison.
I acquired this power within these walls.
There's nothing
I can't accomplish in this world.
I have a bright future.
I'll hand this disc over to Whitesnake.
Even if I could do it myself.
If I wanted to!
I knew it.
I knew you'd do that.
I was waiting
for you to reload.
I was waiting, with my strings ready,
for you to reload your gun.
And you shot at me.
These strings!
When did you do that?
Stone Free!
What?
You're the one in a complete vacuum.
Now,
without a spacesuit,
your blood vessels are going to burst
because your blood will boil in no time!
We've won!
If you want to live,
release this room from your power!
Damn it!
I was sentenced
for how many stab wounds, again?
When I killed that teacher,
the prosecutor said
I stabbed her 69 times.
This urge.
It's surging up in me again.
Shit.
I won't let you underestimate me.
Bitch!
The reaction between hydrogen peroxide
and manganese dioxide
produces oxygen.
Plenty of oxygen in this flask!
Enough to satisfy my slaughter urge
like last time!
Take this!
With this glass, I'm going to turn
your piss-filled body
into a tombstone!
Jolyne Kujo,
your vessels will burst first
since you're wounded all over!
I'm incarcerated for murder, you know.
I'll kill you, and when I leave
this room, I'll be invincible!
Take this.
That should be enough
to get the disc back
from that scumbag's hands.
Weather Report!
What?
Damn it, my body's reached its limit!
If I deactivate my power,
there'll be a huge rush of air.
Maybe I can escape
with the air current.
Zero gravity, deactivated!
Jumpin' Jack Flash!
You should have deactivated it
as soon as you had the chance.
The pressure gradient
would have let you escape.
If only you had done that
while Stone Free was far away...
The air current is pushing you back to me!
When is the Speedwagon Foundation arriving?
In three minutes? Or two?
There's a corridor behind this door.
On the right,
windows overlook the courtyard.
You'll be able to see
the gate leading to the revolving door.
The revolving door leads to the courtyard.
It's accessible during the day,
and it's not locked.
The next challenge is opening this door.
I'll have a guard open it.
We have his work permit.
We'll force a guard to open it.
I see.
Once the door is open,
you knock out the guards
and rush to the courtyard.
Very well.
You'll be convicted
for attempted escape
but also thrown in solitary
for six months,
where you won't even
be able to get enough exercise.
Doesn't matter.
I'm going to the courtyard
to hand this disc to someone
from the Speedwagon Foundation.
That's my only mission in life
right now.
The guards are coming.
Weather Report,
go hide somewhere.
I'll manage on my own.
You're seriously wounded,
and if the guards see your wounds,
they might close the gate.
All right. I understand.
What's going on?
Why are you banging like that?
Oh, it's you.
"Oh, it's you"?
What's going on, Rangler?
What's all this noise?
Wait, I'm opening.
Since you're going back
to the men's prison,
Lang Rangler,
why don't we take a little break
at the chapel?
There are things I need to discuss with you.
That's not a guard!
Who's that guy?
Neither a guard nor an inmate!
What's that uniform?
Même si tu penses que je fais face
Although you think I cope
Ma tête est remplie d'espoir
My head is filled with hope
D'un quelconque endroit autre qu'ici
Of some place other than here
Même si tu penses que je souris
Although you think I smile
Intérieurement et pendant tout ce temps
Inside and all the while
Je m'interroge sur mon destin
I'm wondering about my destiny
Je pense à
I'm thinking about
Toutes les choses
All the things
Que j'aimerais faire
I'd like to do
Dans ma vie
In my life
Je suis un rêveur
I'm a dreamer
Un lointain songeur
A distant dreamer
Rêvant d'espoir
Dreaming far away
Dès à présent
From today
Storm Warning